In recent years, researchers from diverse fields have agreed that short-termism is now a significant problem in industrialised societies.
近年来，不同领域的研究者一致认为，短视主义如今已成为工业化社会的一个重大问题。
The inability to engage with longer-term causes and consequences leads to some of the world’s most serious problems: climate change, biodiversity collapse, and more.
无法关注更长远的原因和后果，导致了世界上一些最严重的问题：气候变化、生物多样性崩溃，等等。
The historian Francis Cole argues that the West has entered a period where “only the present exists, a present characterised at once by the cruelty of the instant and by the boredom of an unending now”.
历史学家弗朗西斯·科尔认为，西方已进入这样一个时期：“只有当下存在，而这个当下的特征既是瞬间的残酷，又是无尽此刻的乏味”。
It has been proved that people have a bias towards the present, focusing on loud attractions in the moment at the expense of the health, well-being and financial stability of their future selves or community.
已经证实，人们存在偏向当下的倾向：他们专注于眼前喧闹的诱惑，却以牺牲未来的自己或未来社群的健康、福祉和财务稳定为代价。
In business, this bias surfaces as short-sighted decisions.
在商业中，这种偏向表现为短视的决策。
And on slow-burning problems like climate change, it translates into the unwillingness to make small sacrifices today that could make a major difference tomorrow.
而在气候变化这类缓慢恶化的问题上，它就表现为人们不愿在今天做出小小的牺牲，而这些牺牲可能在明天带来重大改变。
Instead, all that matters is next quarter’s profit, or satisfying some other near-term desires.
相反，人们只在乎下一季度的利润，或是满足其他某些眼前的欲望。
These biased perspectives cannot be blamed on one single cause.
这些带有偏向的看法不能归咎于单一原因。
It is fair to say, though, that our psychological biases play a major role.
不过，平心而论，我们的心理偏向起着重要作用。
People’s hesitancy to delay satisfaction is the most obvious example, but there are others.
人们不愿延迟满足是最明显的例子，但例子不止这一个。
One of them is about how the most accessible information in the present affects decisions about the future.
其中一种偏向涉及当下最容易获取的信息如何影响有关未来的决策。
For instance, you might hear someone say: “It’s cold this winter, so I needn’t worry about global warming.”
比如，你可能会听到有人说：“今年冬天很冷，所以我不必担心全球变暖。”
Another is that loud and urgent matters are given too much importance, making people ignore longer-term trends that arguably matter more.
另一种是人们过分看重喧闹而紧迫的事情，从而忽视了那些可以说更为重要的长期趋势。
This is when a pop star draws far more attention than, say, gradual biodiversity decline.
这时就会出现这样的情况：一位流行歌星远比诸如生物多样性逐渐减少之类的问题更受关注。
As a psychologist once joked, if aliens wanted to weaken humanity, they wouldn’t send ships; they would invent climate change.
一位心理学家曾开玩笑说，如果外星人想削弱人类，他们不会派飞船来，而是会发明气候变化。
Indeed, when it comes to environmental transformations, we can develop a form of collective “poor memory”, and each new generation can believe the state of affairs they encounter is nothing out of the ordinary.
的确，说到环境变化，我们可能会形成某种集体性的“记性差”，而每一代新人都可能认为，自己所遇到的状况没有什么不寻常。
Older people today, for example, can remember a time with insect-covered car windscreens after long drives.
比如，如今上了年纪的人能记得那样一个年代：长途驾车之后，汽车挡风玻璃上会布满昆虫。
Children, on the other hand, have no idea that the insect population has dropped dramatically.
而孩子们则不知道，昆虫的数量已经急剧下降。